where the struggle
is kind of
the point, right?
It's like building
a muscle. Yeah.
I can think
of so many
times in my
life where the
reason why I
was doing something
was not the
output, it was
the- fact that
I was trying
so hard to
do it. There's
one example in
the Tim Ferriss
interview where you
talked about your
kids struggling to
articulate themselves
emotionally. Mm-hmm.
And adults very
much have the
same problem. Mm-hmm.
And you talked
about AI as
a way to
help them articulate
those emotions. Yeah.
And I thought
about all of
the many times
in my life
where I have
struggled to articulate
my emotions and
how I really
could've used some
help in those
moments. And I
also found myself
thinking about the
times when that
was really
building a muscle.
Where the act
of struggling to
communicate with someone
and- understand what
they wanted from
me was important
to my
development. Mm-hmm.
And so my
question is, if
you think about
that as a
spectrum between things
that are really
important to our
humanity, and the
struggle being removed
is helpful, versus
things where the
struggle is the
point, and
it unlocks
something about our
humanity and is
important to preserve,
like building- Yeah
muscle. How do
you draw the
line between
those things?
And how do
we ensure that
the muscles that
we're building for
this future are
stronger and not
weaker? Yeah,
it's interesting.
I think we're
always going to
find new things
to struggle with.